funfunky.com 2018-05-13

# FunFunky.com Privacy Policy

**FunFunky.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.FunFunky.com

**Right to Change Policy**

  As FunFunky.com is constantly innovating and enhancing the type of services it provides to its users, this Privacy Statement will also continue to change to match the services and features we make available. As such, we reserve the right to change this statement to match the services we provide. If we make any material change to this statement, we will change the date at the top of this statement to reflect the effective date of the change. When you visit our site or use our services and site features, we encourage you to check the date of this Privacy Statement to ensure you are aware of any updates. However, regardless of how this Privacy Statement may change or evolve over time, FunFunky.com will not collect or maintain your private and personally identifiable information without your consent. Further, if you consent to give us your personal information, we will keep it confidential and will not sell, license or disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, unless we are compelled to do so under the law or to comply with court order.

**Types of Information We Collect  
**  
Generally, you are free to browse the FunFunky.com site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or email address) when you visit the FunFunky.com, unless you register or have registered to use our message boards, or otherwise agree to submit to us such information.

**Information Automatically Logged  
**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

**Password Encryption  
**  
Please note that registration in our message boards require that you specify a password for your use. This password is then encrypted by our forums automatically, which means that the staff of FunFunky.com does not have access or knowledge of what your exact password is. This gives you ample security in case you are using the same password repeatedly in other sites (which is strongly discouraged).

**What are Cookies? Why do we use them?  
**  
Various methods are employed to gather this data. "Cookies" are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are "small strings of text" that are stored in browsers; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so.

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. 

**Information on Advertisers/Sponsors  
**  
We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information.

To find out more about how the ad network manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to :

[Google](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html) and [Doubleclick Dart Cookies](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the [NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf) (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time.

 **External Links  
**  
This site contains links to other sites. FunFunky.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Public Forums  
**  
This site makes chat rooms, message boards, and/or other news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Security  
**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

 **Postings on Message Boards  
**  
It is important for you to remain aware that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on any message board, that information is available to any other person or user having access and use of that message board, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage you from offering any personally identifying information within a posting to any message board.

 **Data Quality/Access  
**  
This site gives users the option of changing and modifying information previously provided. Visit your profile to change information.

 **Your Consent to this Policy  
**  
By using our Site, you agree to this Policy. This document supersedes any prior communication on this topic and reflects the entire and exclusive Privacy Policy for this Site. We may change our Policy by posting a new version of it on our Site at any time.

 **Contacting the Web Site  
**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can reach us through email - admin@FunFunky.com
